다이간다는 방을 밝게 하고 적당히 떨어져서 봐!
Watch Daigunder in a bright room and keep some distance!
Смотри Дайгандера со включённым светом, сидя подальше от экрана!
다이간다!
Daigunder!
Дайгандер!
다다다다다다다다다!
Dadadada da da da dada
Дададада-да-да-да-дада!
다다다다다다다다다!
Dadadada da da da dada
Дададада-да-да-да-дада!
다이 다이 다이 다이 다이간다
Dai Dai Dai Dai Daigunder
Дай-Дай-Дай-Дай-Дайгандер
불타라 불타올라라
Burn and flare up
Пыл борьбы разожги ты в себе,
마음의 눈을 열어라
Open your eyes of soul
Распахни шире око души
폭투선언 다이간다
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder!
(Bakutou Sengen Daigunder)
Боевой претендент Дайгандер!
뜨거운 마음을 담아
With all your hot heart
Пусть меня охватит твой жар сердца,
오늘도 기적을 맹새해
I will make a miracle today too
Чтобы сотворить сумел я чудо
드래곤 소드 작렬이야
Dragon Sword bursts
Вспыхнет ярким светом Меч Дракона!
싸워야 할 라이벌은
The rival I have to fight against is
Побороть я должен свой упавший дух,
좌절하려는 내 자신
right here, dispirited myself
что пути к успеху преграждает мне,
어제보다도 진화해서
Evolve even more than yesterday
Вырасти сегодня больше, чем вчера
강해져라!
And become strong!
И сильнее стать!
다다다다 다 다 다 다다
Dadadada da da da dada
Дададада-да-да-да-дада!
드래곤 캐논!
Dragon Cannon!
Пушка Дракона!
다이 다이 다이 다이 다이간다
Dai Dai Dai Dai Daigunder
Дай-Дай-Дай-Дай-Дайгандер
불타라 불타올라라
Burn and flare up
Пыл борьбы разожги ты в себе
에너지 전개로
Open up all your energy and
Дай энергии выход, сказав...
다다다다다다 다
Dadadadadada da
Дададададада-да!!
다이 다이 다이 다이 다이간다
Dai Dai Dai Dai Daigunder
Дай-Дай-Дай-Дай-Дайгандер
쓰러트려라 타도해라
Defeat and knock down
Победи и врагов одолей
빛나는 강철의
Fighter of shining steel
Сталью сверкает тело твоё,
폭투선언 다이간다
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder
Боевой претендент Дайгандер
ダイガンダー！ヘッド合体！
伝説の爆闘神、ドラゴンダイガンダー！
アタック！
アキラ。
リューグ！
俺たちはパートナーだろ？
ああ、そして、
無敵の、
チームアキラだ！
ドラゴンリボルバー！
ドラゴフレーム、ドラゴフリーザ、私の盾となる。
崇高なる目的の犠牲となるのだ！
ダイガンダー！
いつか必ずお前を手に入れて見せるわ！
제 27 화
The 27th Episode
Эпизод 27
도전선언!
Challenge Declaration!
새로운 친구!!
New Friends!!
(en: The Battle for Ryugu)
구동계 체크 완료. 명령 전달계, 이상 없음.
Actuators check complete. Command communication unit, no problem.
동체에 피해가 조금 있긴 한데 곧 수리 가능해요.
Their chassis are damaged a bit, but they can be repaired easily.
잘 되었네요. 드라고플레임하고 드라고프리저가 무사해서.
It's great to know Dragoflame and Dragofreezer are safe.
몸은 문제 있을 리 없다. 그렇지만 문제는 마음이지.
I didn't worry about their bodies at all, but the problem lies in their hearts.
마음?
Hearts?
둘은 지금까지 쭉 드라고버스트의 명령에 따라 활동해 왔다.
Those two have been moving under the order of Dragoburst.
ドラゴフレーム！ドラゴフリーザ！そこどけ！
彼らは私の手足。貴様の命令など聞かぬ。
그렇지만 지금부터는 자신의 의지로 행동하며 살아가야 한다. 옳은 것, 잘못된 것, 각자 판단해서 살아가는 것이다.
But they have to live by their own will and decision. They will decide what's right and wrong by themselves.
과연 둘에게 그게 가능할지는.
I do not know if that's possible to them.
메카 체크 시간이야. 가자, 서봇.
It's time for machine check. Let's go, Supbot.
드라고버스트와의 싸움으로 모두 꽤나 피해를 입었구나.
Everyone is damaged because of the fight against Dragoburst.
그건 얼마 안 가 회복되겠지만 류구가 걱정되는구나.
That will be repaired soon, but I'm worried about Ryugu.
드래곤 다이간다가 되었던 충격에서 어서 재기하면 좋겠지만...
I hope he can recover from the shock of becoming Dragon Daigunder...
기분 좋다.
What a good weather!
그러게.
Yeah.
류구?
Ryugu?
나는... 난 모두를, 아키라를 공격하고 말았어.
I... I attacked everyone, and especially you, Akira.
팀메이트. 친구에게 그런 짓을 하다니 난... 난...
How could I do that to my teammates and friends?!
잊어버려. 네가 잘못한 게 아니야. 네 탓이 아니야. 그러니까 떠올릴 필요 없어!
Forget it. It's not your fault. You did nothing wrong. You don't have to keep remembering that!
그래도...
But...
좀 쉬고 다시 트레이닝이야! 타이탄 클라우더를 얻기 위해 힘내자!
Take some rest, and we'll begin training again! Let's do our best for Titan Clouder!
아니, 그럴 수는 없어. 드라고버스트는 날 포기한 게 아니야. 분명 다시 잡으러 올 거야.
No, I can't do that. Dragoburst didn't give up on me yet. He's going to get me again.
지금 내 힘으로는 놈에게 이길 수 없어. 분명 또 합체하게 되고 말 거야.
I can't defeat him with my current power. I'll end up being combined again.
그리고 너희를 공격하게 될 거야.
And then I'll attack you guys.
류구.
Ryugu.
나는... 난 대체 어째야 좋아...
What... What I should do from now on?
드라고버스트. 대체 어디에 갔나.
Where did that Dragoburst go?
드라고버스트를 유인할, 아, 굿 아이디어가 있소!
I have a good idea to, ah, lure out Dragoburst!
뭐?
What?
놈이 노리는 건 다이간다를 파트너로 하는 것이오!
What he's trying to do is make Daigunder into his partner!
그 즉, 다이간다를 잡으면, 아, 꼭 쫒아 올 것이오!
That means, if we get Daigunder, ah, then he'll definitely come get him!
다이간다를 잡는다? 그건 크게 어렵다.
You're gonna get Daigunder? That will be very difficult.
괜찮소. 소인에게 맡기시오!
Don't worry. Leave that to us-gozaru!
이 날을 위해, 아, 다이간다의 배틀 영상을 막 모았소!
For this day, ah, we've collected Daigunder's battle videos as much as we could!
이걸로 다이간다를 분석해 약점을 찾아 잡아오는 것이오!
We'll analyze Daigunder with this, and go get him using his weak points-gozaru!
일단 록코타운 토너먼트부터!
Let us begin with Rokkotown Tournament!
팀 스스무와의 배틀 로봇 매치. 강력한 초음파가, 아, 류구와 본렉스의 움직임을 막았소이다!
The battle robot match against Team Susumu. A strong supersonic wave, ah, immobilized Ryugu and Bonerex!
でもどうして？あんなホイッスル、データになかったわ。
前方よし！～、リニアMT、現物排除！
팀 스스무 특기의 콤비네이션 공격. 팀 아키라를 궁지에 몰아넣었소!
Team Susumu's specialty move, Combination Attack. It really cornered Team Akira-gozaru!
그렇지만이오!
But-gozaru!
ダイガンダー！合体解除！
ボーンレックス！お前の出番だ！
何？
ダイガレックスで行くぞ！
うん！
일어나라! 승리를 노려라! 뜨거워지는 고상한 열정
Stand up! Aim for the victory! The sublime passion is heating up
Встань и борись! К победе стремись! Горячая страсть нам сердца раскаляет!
ボーンレックス！ガンダー！ヘッド合体！
얼마이고 상처나도 진정한 강함을 알 때까지
No matter how it hurts, until we grasp the true strength
Пусть раны болят, не заметим того, и силы в себе, невиданные, откроем мы!
剣闘王ダイガレックス！
ダイガレックス、デゴイチJK後部の右～を攻撃だ！
OK!
デスペクター！トライホーン！離脱しろ！
Ok,コマンダー！
숨이 멎는 배틀, 피말리는 순간이 나를 불러
Breathtaking battle! The moment on the edge is calling me
Голову битва вскружит! Держимся на краю! Азарта миг с собой вдруг позовёт
얼빠진 짓만 하고 있을 수는 없어 쓰려진다면 몇번이라도
No blunders anymore. No matter the number defeated,
Промашек мы больше с тобой не допустим, неважно, как много нас ждёт врагов.
いけ！ダイガレックス！
れっくじゅうじゃんけん！
일어나라! 승리를 노려라! 뜨거워지는 고상한 열정
Stand up! Aim for the victory! The sublime passion is heating up
Встань и борись! К победе стремись! Горячая страсть нам сердца раскаляет!
donna ni kizutsuite mo hitasura ni jibun jishin wo shinjite
얼마이고 상처나도 오로지 자기 자신을 믿어
No matter how it hurts, we believe in nothing but ourselves
<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<INSERT HERE>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>
かまたき！
今だ！ダイガレックス！合体解除！
合体解除！
リューグ！ガンダー！ヘッド合体！
爆闘王ダイガンダー！
デゴイチJK,リニアMT,地上速度で攻撃だ！
デスペクター！トライホーン！
ダイガンダー！
ドラゴンキャノン！
アタック！
ヒットポイントゼロ。デゴイチJK、リニアMTダウン。ウィナー、チームアキラ！
やったぜ！
俺たち骨太ぞ！
패배의 원인은, 아, 다이노 유닛을 얕잡아 보아서.
The reason of defeat is, ah, they looked down of Dino Unit.
분명 본렉스의 힘은 얕볼 수 없다.
You're right in that Bonerex's power isn't something easy.
거기서 계속해서, 알바트로스 리그에서의 영상이오!
Continuing from that, it's a video from Albatross League-gozaru!
あ、チームアキラの先制攻撃だ！
～です。転に祈りをささげチャンスを待つのです。
素早いダッシュ。いけるわ。
준결승. 아, 팀 블루즈와의 대전이오.
Semi-finals. It was a match with Team Blues.
가짜 서봇을 쓴 소인들의 작전이 폭렬한 전투였소!
It was a battle where our plan of using imitation Supbot worked marvelously!
リューグ！ボーンレックス！どうした！
どうもこうもねぇ。
か、体が！体の自由が！
聞かない！
な、何？！
ファイターチェンジ！
死神貴族、デスペクター！ そして、怪力門番、トライホーン！
今の私たちには武装は無用。ただ、ただ祈るのみです。
デスペクター！トライホーン！リューグとボーンレックスの闘いを止めるんだ！
OK!
なんだって？！
폭투선언 다이간다
Bakutou Sengen Daigunder
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder
Боевой претендент Дайгандер
by Subdivers
Russian TL by SutoKuroi
Subdivers 번역
폭투선언 다이간다
Bakutou Sengen Daigunder
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder
Боевой претендент Дайгандер
by Subdivers
Russian TL by SutoKuroi
Subdivers 번역
ドラゴンキャノン！
待て！ダイガンダー！
가짜 서봇에게 조종당해, 아, 팀 아키라는 서로 공격!
Controlled by imitation Supbot, ah, Team Akira attacks each other!
やめろ！やめるんだ！
그래, 그래, 반격이오! 팀 블루즈이오!
Yes, yes do counterattack-gozaru! Team Blues-gozaru!
ジャッキー一号、二号、戦闘開始！
みんな、頑張れ！耐えるんだ！
우리 작전으로, 팀 아키라는 패배 직전!
By our plan, Team Akira is about to lose!
그렇지만, 가짜 서봇 작전은 들키고 말았소!
But sadly imitation Supbot plan has been discovered!
か、体が動くぞ！
偽サボットは破壊したわ。ダイガンダーたちは、もう自由よ。
よし！クラスターパワー全開！
ドラゴンキャノン！
アタック！
ヒットポイントゼロ。ジャッキー一号、二号、ダウン。ウィンナー、チームアキラ！
気圧８００ｈPa!ハリケーンパワーアップ！
계속해 결승전은 팀 오발과의 대전이었소.
Following, the final was the match against Team Oval.
날씨를 자유자재로 조종하는 초강적이었소!
They were strong enemeis who could control weather freely!
何？！
リューグ！
みんな！
私たちは観測データにもとずき、攻撃犯意と被害状況を設定する。もはや君たちに勝ち目はない！
みんな！一時退却だ！
アニマルユニット、ヒットポイントゼロ。
しまった！
おっと、アニマルユニット、ダウンだ！
ブライオン！イーグルアロー！ドリモーグ！
こうなったらダイガンダーで勝負だ！
リューグ！ガンダー！ヘッド合体！
爆闘王ダイガンダー！
ダイガンダー！ドラゴンキャノンだ！
ドラゴンキャノン！
ダイガンダー！
ハルカが、サボットが、ダイノユニットが、ギンザンが、チームメートが、ライバルが！
俺たちを支えてる、守ってるくれているんだ！
仲間の喜びを、仲間の怒りをパワーに帰るんだ！
立て！ダイガンダー！
またそんなパワーが残って言ったのは！
ドラゴンソード！
バカな！ハリケーンアタックの破壊力はダイガンダーの防御力をはるかに敬ってるはずだ！
クラスターパワー全開！
ドラゴンキャノン！
アタック！
ひまわりJP!のあUS!
ヒットポイントゼロ。ひまわりJP、のあUS、ダウン。ウィンナー、チームアキラだ！
やったぜ！
결국 어느 싸움도, 아, 다이간다가 승리했소.
At last, in every fight, ah, Daigunder won.
그렇지만 놈의 약점은 충분히 깨달았소!
But still, we figured out his weak points pretty well!
최신 정보다. 팀 아키라의 애니멀 유닛, 다이노 유닛이 기계 정비 중이다.
New information for you. Team Akira's Animal Unit and Dino Unit are undergoing maintenance.
-그 말은, 아, 즉,
-활동 가능한 건 다이간다 뿐이라는 것이오!
-That means, ah, simply,
-Only Daigunder can move now-gozaru!
찬스!
Chance!
둘 다 발밑 조심해라!
Both of you, be careful with your steps!
드라고플레임! 드라고프리저!
Dragoflame! Dragofreezer!
어, 아키라!
Hey, Akira!
너희들 건강해졌구나!
You guys are fine!
조금 산책시키려고 말이야.
I was going to take them for a walk.
잘 됐네. 이걸로 같이 싸울 수 있겠어!
Great! We'll be able to fight together from now on!
오늘부터 너희는 팀 아키라의 일원! 내 팀메이트야! 함께 힘내자!
From now on, you guys are members of Team Akira! Let's do our best together!
전투 능력으로 보면 둘은 다이간다 유닛의 일원이 되는 게 제일 좋겠지.
Judging from their battle capacity, they are best suited to be in Daigunder Unit.
우리 일원?
One of us?
그래. 검과 방패로 체인지해서 다이간다의 새 무기가 되는 거야.
Yes. They will change into a sword and a shield, to become new weapons of Daigunder.
그렇게 엿장수 마음대로는, 아, 안 되오!
It's not going to be, ah, easy!
타이거마루! 로우가마루!
Tigermaru! Rougamaru!
류구와 건더! 아니, 다이간다는 가져가겠소!
We'll take Ryugu and Gunder, no, Daigunder-gozaru!
뭐라고?!
What?!
스위치 온이오!
Switch on-gozaru!
뭐야?
What's that?
전방각으로 손가락질 방향으로, 아, 발사!
Towards us, to where I'm pointing to, ah, fire!
초음파... 안 움직여져...
Supersonic wave... I can't move...
전진!
Advance!
류구! 건더!
Ryugu! Gunder!
드라고플레임! 드라고버스트! 뒤로 가라!
Dragoflamee! Dragoburst! Go back!
이 공격, 이 위력! 팀 스스무 때하고 똑같아!
This attack and this might! This is exactly same with how it was with Team Susumu!
그렇지. 그들의 공격을 철저히 분석한, 아, 복습해서 만든 기계다.
Exactly. We've analyazed their attacks, ah, and finally made this machine!
자, 출력을 올리오!
Let me make it more powerful-gozaru!
류구! 건더!
Ryugu! Gunder!
힘내라! 초음파에서 탈출해라!
Keep it up! Get out of the supersonic wave!
아, 그러지 못할 테오!
ah, you won't do that!
어딜 갈 생각을-
Where do you think you're-
아니, 움직일 수가 없소.
Er, we can't move!
이, 이건 나쁜 생각이었소!
T- that was a bad idea-gozaru!
-아키라! 지금이다!
-좋아!
-Akira! Now!
-Right!
류구! 건더! 헤드합체!
Ryugu! Gunder! Head Fusion
폭투왕 다이간다!
Wild Fight King Daigunder!
다이간다! 드래곤 소드야!
Daigunder! Use Dragon Sword!
드래곤 소드!
Dragon Sword!
에잇, 아, 다음 작전이오!
Damn! ah, next plan!
알겠소!
Understood-gozaru!
기압 800hPa, 허리케인 공격!
Atmospheric pressure 800hPa! Hurricane Attack!
자, 스위치 온!
Switch on!
보쇼! 팀 오발에 맞먹는 날씨 공격이오!
Look! It's weather attack, just like Team Oval's-gozaru!
지면 안 돼, 다이간다!
Don't lose, Daigunder!
다이간다!
Daigunder!
작전 대성공! 덤으로 놈들도 가져가겠소!
Plan successful! We'll take them in addition!
드라고플레임과 드라고프리저, 드라고버스트를 끌어들일 미끼가 되시오!
Dragoflame and Dragofreezer, become the bait to lure Dragoburst-gozaru!
그렇소!
He's right!
포획 네트 발사!
Capturing net, fire!
안 돼!
No!
아키라!
Akira!
뭣이?!
What?!
둘은 우리 친구야! 팀메이트야! 너희에게 넘겨줄까보냐!
Those two are my friends! My teammates! I won't let you take them!
그럼 힘으로라도 뺏겠소!
Then we'll take them by force!
그렇지만 그 전에, 아, 방해꾼은 퇴장시키겠소!
But before that, ah, we'll get rid of any hindrances!
드라고플레임! 드라고프리저!
Dragoflame! Dragofreezer!
뭣이?!
What?!
같이 싸우자! 파이터 체인지야!
Let's fight together! Do Fighter Change!
위험한 배틀 헤어나가라 내일로 대시야
Go through dangerous battles; dash towards tomorrow
Проходи сквозь опасные битвы, мчась навстречу новому дню
클러스터 파워 전개!
Activate Cluster Powers!
달려나가라 겁내지 마라 자신을 믿어라
Run away! Don't be afraid! Believe in yourself!
Смело беги, не страшась ничего, и веру закали свою!
다이간다! 드라고플레임하고 드라고프리저로 무장해!
Daigunder! Arm with Dragoflame and Dragofreezer!
파워 승부라면 지지 않는다 잘 알아두어라
You do not lose in power battle; bear this fact deep in mind
Нет поражения в битве сильнейших, крепко запомни сей факт
세이버 체인지!
Saber Change!
실드 체인지!
Shield Change!
정정당당 파이트 불태워 부딪혀라
Fair and square, fight! Burn up and clash against!
В схватку открыто и честно вступая, не сдавай ни шагу назад!
날려버려라 라이벌을 전광석화의 날랜 솜씨
Throw away your rival, in the nimbleness of lightning!
Прочь смети соперника, молниеносной атакой сразив!
무무슨! 드라고플레임과 드라고프리저가 다이간다하고 합체했소!
How this could be?! Dragoflame and Dragofreezer have combined with Daigunder!
투지를 불태워라 BURNING HEART
Burn the fighting spirit! BURNING HEART
Боевой дух разожжёт СЕРДЦА ЖАР!
이렇게 된 바, 아, 정정당당히 정면공격을!
This means, ah, we'll have to attack from front fair and square!
타이거 타츠마키기리!
Tiger Tatsumakigiri!
로우가 미카즈키기리!
Rouga Mikazukigiri!
끊어버려라! 뛰쳐나와라! 움켜잡아라 내일의 영광
Break through! Fly out! Grasp the glory of tomorrow
Страх смахни! Вперёд лети! Ветра горячий порыв ощути
다이간다! 필살 드래곤 버스터!
Daigunder! Finisher, Dragon Buster!
덤벼들어라 전부 모아 앞서 움직여 끝장내주마
Come and fight! You'll finish all of them before anyone does!
В бой без промедлений! Всех ты одолеешь, во мгновенье ока вырываясь вперёд!
날려버려라 라이벌을 전광석화의 날랜 솜씨
Throw away your rival, in the nimbleness of lightning!
Прочь смети соперника, молниеносной атакой сразив!
비스트 체인지!
Beast Change!
투지를 불태워라 BURNING HEART
Burn the fighting spirit! BURNING HEART
Боевой дух разожжёт СЕРДЦА ЖАР!
이 빛은 꼭 갚겠소!
We'll pay back this someday!
기억해 두시오!
Remember this-gozaru!
해냈어!
We did it!
대체 뭔 일이야?
What happened here?
드라고플레임하고 드라고프리저가 팀 아키라의 일원이 되었다. 그걸 축하하던 참이야.
Dragoflame and Dragofreezer became members of Team Akira. We were celebrating that.
둘이 팀 아키라에?
Those two will join Team Akira?
보아하니 새로운 힘이 필요한 것 같구나. 다이간다를 쓰러트리고 드라고버스트를 날려버릴 압도적인 힘이.
It seems that I need a power. A overwhelming power that will take Daigunder down and throw away Dragoburst.
드라고버스트가 어디 있는지 알게 되면 곧 연락할 테니까.
I'll let you know as soon as I find out where Dragoburst is.
저희도 뭔가 정보를 얻으면 박사님께 알려 드릴게요.
We'll let you know too if we find out something.
그래, 부탁한다!
Yeah, please do so!
다들 안녕이다!
Then bye, everyone!
안녕, 할아버지!
Bye-bye, grandpa!
조심해!
Be careful!
아키라, 나 힘낼게. 드라고버스트에게 지지 않도록 몸도 마음도 단련할게.
Akira, I'll do my best to train myself so that I don't lose to Dragoburst physically or mentally.
나도 하나부터 다시 할게! 더더욱 강해져서 드라고버스트를 동료로 맞이하자!
I'll start over again! Let's become stronger and welcome Dragoburst as our friend!
그리고 언젠가 타이탄 클라우더를 손에 넣는 거야!
And we'll get that Titan Clouder into our hands someday!
그래!
Right!
끝없는 꿈을 꾸고 있어
Dreaming an endless dream
Я сон бесконечный вижу опять перед собой
몇번이고 쓰러져도
I fall down over and over again
Как упал, и лечу вниз вновь и вновь.
저 구름 위에는 분명히
Up over those clouds
Там, где-то в высотах, за чертой облаков
푸른 하늘이 펼쳐져 있을 거야
a blue sky awaits
голубое небо ждёт меня!
강해지기 위해서라면 누구도 혼자서는
To be strong, nobody can ever become
Сильным быть, чтоб никто превзойти не смог
강해지고 뜨거워질 수 없어
strong and hot, by oneself
Стать сильней, горячей, сам я хочу!
불꽃의 Fight Fight Fighting soul
Flaming fightin' fightin' fighting soul
Так гори, душа, душа бойца!
용기를 마주치는 그 때
When you face your courage
Смелость повстречай, и пусть ведёт она тебя в жизни.
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
느껴져 바로 너라는 게
I can feel it, yes, it's you
Я это чувствую, да, это ты!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
둘은 서로의 영웅
The two are heroes of each other
Два героя - части одного, нерушимы связи,
질 수 없는 같은 내일을
They run towards to the same tomorrow
Вместе в новый день по одной тропе спешат
바라보고 달려
that they cannot lose
И не собьются с неё!
하루카가 아키라하고 싸우고 다이랜드에서 나가 버렸어.
Haruka has fought with Akira, and left Dailand.
아키라는 하루카 따위 없어도 문제 없다는데, 괜찮아?
Akira says that it'll be alright without Haruka, but really?
괜찮아, 괜찮아!
It's alright, it's alright!
트레이닝 배틀 스케줄은?
What about schedules for training battles?
괜찮아, 괜찮아!
It's alright, it's alright!
얘들 메인터넌스는?
What about our maintenance?
괜찮아, 괜찮아!
It's alright, it's alright!
에너지 팩 수급은?
What about energy pack supply?
괜찮아, 괜찮아!
It's alright, it's alright!
아, 그러고 보니 배고프다, 류구.
Oh, by the way, I'm hungry, Ryugu.
으악! 밥이 하나도 없어!
Agh! There's no food here!
폭투선언 다이간다의 다음 이야기!
전직선언! 하루카는 일류 매니저!!
Next time on Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder!
Job Change Declaration! Haruka is First Class Manager!!